[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "The charter Tony Soprano in the lexicon of television?", "question_tokens": ["The", "charter", "Tony", "Soprano", "in", "the", "lexicon", "of", "television", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I think it's at the top because I think, you know, television forever was, you know, consumed with creating a lead charter who would be, you know, likable and I think he made him -- he made this incredibly scary guy, who in many ways, extremely likable at the same time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "at", "the", "top", "because", "I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "television", "forever", "was", ",", "you", "know", ",", "consumed", "with", "creating", "a", "lead", "charter", "who", "would", "be", ",", "you", "know", ",", "likable", "and", "I", "think", "he", "made", "him", "--", "he", "made", "this", "incredibly", "scary", "guy", ",", "who", "in", "many", "ways", ",", "extremely", "likable", "at", "the", "same", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tony Soprano"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "What kind of shape was he in there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "shape", "was", "he", "in", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "He was -- he was in a jovial mood, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "--", "he", "was", "in", "a", "jovial", "mood", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "I would agree completely with that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "agree", "completely", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "But what is your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "is", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Well, I was shocked.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "shocked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Well, it will be right up there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "will", "be", "right", "up", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "You mean like Vegas?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", "like", "Vegas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "No, not Vegas.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "Vegas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "What, you mean like a hospital with the padded rooms and the straight jackets?", "question_tokens": ["What", ",", "you", "mean", "like", "a", "hospital", "with", "the", "padded", "rooms", "and", "the", "straight", "jackets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "No, no straight jackets.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "straight", "jackets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "What are you picking up there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "picking", "up", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Yes, definitely, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "definitely", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James"]}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Were you aware, were the cast aware of any health issues?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "aware", ",", "were", "the", "cast", "aware", "of", "any", "health", "issues", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Well, at that time -- this -- we worked together a long time ago, and he was -- it's funny because he was just beginning -- when I worked with James, \"The Sopranos\" had not yet aired, so nobody knew what it was.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "at", "that", "time", "--", "this", "--", "we", "worked", "together", "a", "long", "time", "ago", ",", "and", "he", "was", "--", "it", "'s", "funny", "because", "he", "was", "just", "beginning", "--", "when", "I", "worked", "with", "James", ",", "``", "The", "Sopranos", "''", "had", "not", "yet", "aired", ",", "so", "nobody", "knew", "what", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Is that pretty much, Kevin, how all the cast viewed him?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "pretty", "much", ",", "Kevin", ",", "how", "all", "the", "cast", "viewed", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Again, I can't speak for everyone else, but that was certainly the impression I got.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "speak", "for", "everyone", "else", ",", "but", "that", "was", "certainly", "the", "impression", "I", "got", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kevin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "How did Tony Soprano come into your life and into ours?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "Tony", "Soprano", "come", "into", "your", "life", "and", "into", "ours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "I got the script and I remember reading it and I was laughing out loud.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "the", "script", "and", "I", "remember", "reading", "it", "and", "I", "was", "laughing", "out", "loud", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tony Soprano"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "In what way?", "question_tokens": ["In", "what", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "You know, suave, good looking Mafioso guy.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "suave", ",", "good", "looking", "Mafioso", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "What is your reaction to his very sad, untimely death today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "his", "very", "sad", ",", "untimely", "death", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, I'm shocked and I'm, you know, really incredibly sad like everybody else.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "shocked", "and", "I", "'m", ",", "you", "know", ",", "really", "incredibly", "sad", "like", "everybody", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "He didn't seem very fit, and it's probably -- don't want to speculate about what happened to him but in terms of his capacity to do these kind of roles, you as a viewer, what did you -- what did you make of his power as a figure, physically and mentally?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "n't", "seem", "very", "fit", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "probably", "--", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "speculate", "about", "what", "happened", "to", "him", "but", "in", "terms", "of", "his", "capacity", "to", "do", "these", "kind", "of", "roles", ",", "you", "as", "a", "viewer", ",", "what", "did", "you", "--", "what", "did", "you", "make", "of", "his", "power", "as", "a", "figure", ",", "physically", "and", "mentally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "He is very powerful.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "very", "powerful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Quite brooding, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Quite", "brooding", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Jeffrey, we're talking a little bit about \"The Sopranos\" but he was also a great movie actor, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Jeffrey", ",", "we", "'re", "talking", "a", "little", "bit", "about", "``", "The", "Sopranos", "''", "but", "he", "was", "also", "a", "great", "movie", "actor", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "He was.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Why aren't you interested in the guy that's driving the car?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "n't", "you", "interested", "in", "the", "guy", "that", "'s", "driving", "the", "car", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "I think he was taken aback himself by the scale of fame that came with the role and he really, I think, always found that a little awkward to deal with.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "was", "taken", "aback", "himself", "by", "the", "scale", "of", "fame", "that", "came", "with", "the", "role", "and", "he", "really", ",", "I", "think", ",", "always", "found", "that", "a", "little", "awkward", "to", "deal", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]